[{"answer": "These poor bankers.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 1, "question": "Is this the angriest man in America?", "qSentId": 0}, {"answer": "No, I haven't.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "You've calmed down since our last encounter?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, you actually have seen me backstage here.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "I mean what are you like?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Do you ever wish you hadn't decided to embark on this crazy second life?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "I think that this is the Obama that I voted for, and I think the majority of people who voted for him voted for this Obama that -- today he referenced Franklin Roosevelt and that -- and that we have to get out of this mentality we've been in for the last 30 years, as he said, where it's the sort of you're on your own economy.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "What did you make of the speech?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Of where I think you're wrong about the comparison --", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "What are you referencing?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "Well, this is a problem.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "The message has not got through, has it?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "When I -- when I was of college age --", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "But that's not true, though, is it?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Yes, they're -- let me tell you right now.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Do you believe that?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Well, the answer is reality.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "What is the answer then?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Let's turn to the -- let's turn to the real villains.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "How's that?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Well, 25 percent is a lot of people, isn't it?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "The bailouts and so on, should those people who did deliberately really spend beyond their means, should they be bailed out in the way that you're talking about with these foreclosures?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Isn't that -- wouldn't that be the decent thing to do?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "I agree with you.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "What would be wrong with asking for a special prosecutor to investigate how that crash happened in first place?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "-- is an outrage.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Isn't it right?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Well, yes, I went down to Cobb County, Georgia, which he represented in Congress.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "So you and Newt then best buddies?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Well, I have more footage.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Yes, I have all the outtakes that didn't make it on the air.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "There might be, yes.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Is it good stuff?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "I'm not planning on him being the nominee.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Are you planning to release this?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Maybe like a bottle of Chateau (INAUDIBLE), he just got better with age.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "I can't believe he's going to -- how long -- what is the shelf life of a Republican candidate in the number one position this year?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "He's a smart guy.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "He's intelligent?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "But does anything that he said resonate as potentially truthful?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Because it's like last comic standing on your other network that you used to -- it is going to be like the last one standing.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Why is he the front-runner?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Yes, I would be referring to him, who, by the way, was born in my state of Michigan.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Are you referring to Mr. Romney?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "It is true.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Actually that is probably true, isn't it?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "I think Republicans and right wingers, they blow me up into this kind of really mythical, scary character.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "What is the reality about you and your wealth?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "I don't have the number right off hand.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "How much have your movies grossed in total?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Half a billion dollars?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "If you were to leave tomorrow, you'd presumably leave a good old pile, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Absolutely not, no, no, no.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Presumably you don't think everyone in the one percent is evil, do you?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "You know there are good ones.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Can I have their names, please?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "I think that's the way he talked for the first three years.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "I'm going to do that, but I'm not going to demonize you?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "Well, look --", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "If you're carving up Republican responsibility, Democrat and the American public, Wall Street, how would you do it?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "Well, it's only fair in the sense that you have to understand that the Republicans and the Democrats -- and it's mostly Republican, but Democrats have colluded over the years with this.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "That's why I asked you to do a proper pie chart, because I don't think that's fair, is it?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "Good.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "-- for the Republican nominee, what do you think of that?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "Well, one, comedy.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 671, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 670}, {"answer": "Well, \"The Washington post\" three weeks ago had this investigation and they said that President Obama has now raised more money from Wall Street and the banks for this election cycle than all -- than all eight Republicans combined.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "So what is your theory?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "It's fascinating to find out why they're doing it.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "Why are you taking this money?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "Oh, my God.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "I'm going to look you straight in the eye and say, Michael Moore, how many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "Come on.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "Where are you?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "Be honest.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "Properly in love?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "Probably maybe two or three times.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "How many time have you literally felt your heart in your gut?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "Well, she -- in some ways, she's more aggressive than I am.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "ORGAN: How does she put up with you charging around the world trying to put all of the world's problems to right?", "qSentId": 725}, {"answer": "On some of these issues.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 728, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 727}, {"answer": "Well, we don't -- I don't -- we should eat breakfast.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 731, "question": "What the hell's the breakfast table like?", "qSentId": 730}, {"answer": "It's irrelevant to this interview.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 744, "question": "How many times have you been in love?", "qSentId": 743}, {"answer": "I feel that I owe him my love.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 765, "question": "How much do you feel you owe Martin Kindu Isaacs (ph), your husband now?", "qSentId": 764}, {"answer": "I know -- I know it could have been me.", "docId": "111206pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "When you look at what happened to Amy Winehouse, do you think that could have been you if things had played out a different way for you?", "qSentId": 775}]